Is it really true
To rzeczywiście prawda
That's no secret
To żadna tajemnica
What a bastard!
A to bydlak!
Get up, quickly, we have a problem
Wstawaj szybko, mamy problem
Seems like Dar was sniffing around here.
Dar tu był prawdopodobnie.
Our packet of weed have vanished
Paczka ziela nam zniknęła
searching everywhere and can't find it.
szukam wszędzie i jej nie ma.
He must've gone to the farm
Musiał udać się na farmę
maybe I'll find the package there.
myślę, że tam paczkę znajdę.
This is my best weed
To najlepsze moje ziele
and I won't share it with Dar
z Darem nim się nie podzielę
We'll search the forests
Przeszukamy lasy
we will search all the farms
przeszukamy wszystkie farmy
We'll go to the castle
Pójdziemy do zamku
and to the Red Lantern
i do Czerwonej Latarni
We will spend hours
Spędzimy godziny
searching the whole town
przeszukując całe miasto
and If we'll have to
jeśli będzie trzeba
we will search even a monastery
przeszukamy nawet klasztor
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nam towar
tell me, where Dar could have hid it.
powiedz mi, gdzie Dar go schował.
I am looking for a package
Szukam paczki
a tiny one and square-shaped
taka mała, kwadratowa
Perhaps I can help
Może wam pomogę
if there's a reward in it for me.
jeśli w grę wchodzi nagroda.
Leave me alone
Daj mi spokój
I'm having a headache all day.
Od rana boli mnie głowa.
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nam towar
tell me, where Dar could have hid it.
powiedz mi, gdzie Dar go schował.
I am looking for a package
Szukam paczki
a tiny one and square-shaped
taka mała, kwadratowa
Even if I knew
Nawet, gdybym wiedział
I wouldn't say a word
To nie powiem ani słowa
I haven't heard
Nie słyszałem
any rumors about it.
żeby o tym ktoś plotkował.
WHERE IS HE?!
Gdzie on jest?!
We've searched the whole farm
Sprawdziliśmy całą farmę
all the floors, every corridor
wszystkie piętra, każdy parter
No one has seen the mercenary
Nikt nie widział najemnika
that have vanished with our package
który z naszą paczką znika
We won't find anything here
Nic już tutaj nie znajdziemy
it is time to leave this place
czas opuścić te tereny
We must ask everyone
Musimy popytać wszystkich
Dar couldn't have left the island
Dar nie mógł opuścić wyspy
We'll search the forests
Przeszukamy lasy
we will search all the farms
przeszukamy wszystkie farmy
We will go to the castle
Pójdziemy do zamku
and to the Red Lantern
i do Czerwonej Latarni
We will spend hours
Spędzimy godziny
searching the whole town
przeszukując całe miasto
and If we'll have to
jeśli będzie trzeba
we will search even a monastery
przeszukamy nawet klasztor
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nam towar
tell me where Dar could have hid it
powiedz mi, gdzie Dar go schował
I am looking for a package
Szukam paczki
a tiny one and square-shaped
taka mała, kwadratowa
You were supposed to search for dragons
Miałeś szukać smoków
I don't know what you're still doing here
Nie wiem, po co ta rozmowa
Don't disturb me
Nie przeszkadzaj
I must observe the orcs
Muszę orków obserwować
Our stuff got stolen
Ukradli nam towar
tell me, where Dar could have hid it
powiedz mi, gdzie Dar go schował
I'm looking for a package
Szukam paczki
a tiny one and square shaped.
taka mała, kwadratowa
Isn't it that package
Czy to nie ta paczka
you were supposed to confiscate
którą miałeś skonfiskować
Better tell me
Lepiej powiedz mi
if you have seen my liver
gdzie jest moja wątroba
I'm almost certain, that it's here
Jestem prawie pewien, że to tu
my senses lead me here
mnie prowadzą zmysły
a smell of swampweed can be felt
zapach bagiennego ziela czuć
somewhere in this area
w tym rejonie wyspy
You still have one place to check
Musisz jeszcze sprawdzić jedną z dróg
before the night will come
zanim noc zawita
If you'll head down the road
Jeśli tylko pójdziesz drogą w dół
you will find the mercenary
znajdziesz najemnika
What are you going to do about the thief, then?
Co w takim razie zrobisz ze złodziejem?
I'll catch him puffing away on my weed.
Złapię go, jak będzie palił moje ziele.
And then I'll find a quiet spot and teach him a lesson he won't forget.
A wtedy znajdę spokojne miejsce i dam mu lekcję, której nie zapomni.
What do you mean?
To znaczy?
It's quite simple!
To dość proste!
I'LL FLATTEN HIM!
SKASUJĘ GNOJKA!
Translation: Delph, GaroK
Translation: Delph, GaroK
So I've got you after ALL!
A jednak mi się nie wymkniesz!